Guide to the Dairy marketing publications, 1909-2010.
Dairy marketing publications
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Dairy marketing publications, 1909-2010.
21-43-3920
Leland and Novakovic Spencer
23.8 cubic feet.
Publications
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Various publications concerning dairy marketing.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Various publications concerning dairy marketing.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Spencer, Leland and Novakovic, Andrew,
Subjects:
Dairy laws.; Milk--Cooperative marketing.; Milk--Quality.; Milk trade.; Dairying--Economic aspects.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Publications concerning Dairy Marketing, 1917-1939 (Box 1)
- Publications concerning Dairy Marketing, 1932-1954 (Box 2)
- Publications concerning Dairy Marketing, 1948-1957 (Box 3)
- Publications concerning Dairy Marketing, 1915-1959 (Box 4)
- Publications concerning Dairy Marketing, 1940-1955 (Box 5)
- Publications concerning Dairy Marketing, 1956-1959 (Box 6)
- Publications concerning Dairy Marketing, A-Ba (arranged alphabetically) (Box 7)
- Publications concerning Dairy Marketing, Ba-Bl and Ha-Hu (arranged alphabetically) (Box 8)
- Publications concerning Dairy Marketing, Bl-Bo and W-Z (arranged alphabetically) (Box 9)
- Publications concerning Dairy Marketing, Bo-Bu (arranged alphabetically) (Box 10)
- Publications concerning Dairy Marketing, C-Co (arranged alphabetically) (Box 11)
- Publications concerning Dairy Marketing, Co-Do (arranged alphabetically) (Box 12)
- Publications concerning Dairy Marketing, E-Gr (arranged alphabetically) (Box 13)
- Publications concerning Dairy Marketing, Ga-Ha (arranged alphabetically) (Box 14)
- Publications concerning Dairy Marketing, Ja-La and USDA Publications (arranged alphabetically) (Box 15)
- Publications concerning Dairy Marketing, Do, Ki-La (arranged alphabetically) (Box 16)
- Publications concerning Dairy Marketing, Ja-Ne (arranged alphabetically) (Box 17)
- Publications concerning Dairy Marketing, Na-NY (arranged alphabetically) (Box 18)
- Publications concerning Dairy Marketing, Mu-Pr (arranged alphabetically) (Box 19)
- Publications concerning Dairy Marketing, Ms-Su (arranged alphabetically) (Box 20)
- Publications concerning Dairy Marketing, St-US (arranged alphabetically) (Box 21)
- Publications concerning Dairy Marketing, US-Wo (arranged alphabetically) (Box 22)
- Northeast Dairy Conference Proceedings, not complete, 1939-1992 (Box 23)
- Publications concerning Dairy Marketing, no particular order, mostly M's (Box 24-25)
- Dairy Cooperative Coordinating Committee for the Northeast - Minutes, Bylaws, Memos, 1979-1980 (Box 25)